The nose is the most prominent feature of the face.
It is the central point of the face
and it's the feature that can most influence
all the areas in the face.
That is why any change we make to the nose,
no matter how small,
will affect the appearance of your face.
That's why when you're choosing the professional
to perform a rhinoplasty,
it's very important that you make sure
that he or she is qualified
and has the necessary experience
to understand what you want to achieve
and give you a safe and satisfactory result.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm Dr. Fulvio Correa,
a board certified plastic surgeon.
Through our all-inclusive program
that we have designed especially for patients,
come from other countries like you.
My staff will accompany you
in every phase of the journey.
Answering all your questions,
helping you to plan your trip,
scheduling your accommodation in our recovery house,
where you will have all the comforts and care necessary
for a prompt and satisfactory recovery.
Schedule your free evaluation right now
and start your journey to achieve your goals
and boost your confidence.